A Guide to the Norman Sisisky Papers, 1982-2001
Library of Virginia
- Series VI. Speeches, 1983-2000., Extent: 14 boxes. (Box 77-90)
  - Maritime Training Institute (1984). (Box 78, Folder 47)
  - Norfolk Naval Shipyard Apprentice Graduation (1984). (Box 78, Folder 48)
  - 1984 Election Results. (Box 78, Folder 49)
  - Fifth District Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, Danville - (1984). (Box 78, Folder 50)
  - Voting Accessibility/Social Security Disability Reform/Community Living Amendments - Talking Points (1984). (Box 78, Folder 51)
  - Suffolk Farm Bureau (1984). (Box 78, Folder 52)
  - National Park Service, Petersburg Battlefield (1984). (Box 78, Folder 53)
  - Speech Index, 1985-1986. (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - National Civilian Administrators Association Luncheon, Portsmouth - 18 January 1985. (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - VFW Loyalty Day Parade, Hopewell - 28 April 1985. (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Senior Citizens Month: A Celebration of Unity - 3 May 1985. (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Manor High School Graduation - June 1985. (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Association of Non-Profit Homes - 19 July 1985. (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Rural Homesteading Program Lottery, Lawrenceville - 9 August 1985. (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Social Security 50th Anniversary - 14 August 1985. (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Mended Hearts - 19 August 1985. (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Brent Lox and Isle of Wight Social Services - 22-23 August 1985. (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - AFL-CIO - 24 August 1985. (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Cooperative Extension Service - 27 August 1985. (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Healthcare Financial Management Association - 29 August 1985. (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Foster Parents - 3 September 1985. (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - AARP Crater Chapter 1399 - 9 September 1985. (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Petersburg Democratic Party Dinner - 21 September 1985. (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Isle of Wight Volunteer Rescue Squad - 21 September 1985. (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Governor's Conference on Small Business - 27 September 1985. (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - State Mental Health and Mental Retardation Conference, Williamsburg - 4 October 1985. (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Small Business Conference, Longwood College - 4 November 1985. (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Greater Hampton Roads Chamber of Commerce - 10 November 1985. (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Veteran's Day - 11 November 1985. (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Small Business Liability Insurance Hearing, Portsmouth - 18 November 1985. (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Government Purchasing Seminar, Portsmouth - 22 November 1985. (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Petersburg Chamber of Commerce - 4 December 1985. (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Tidewater Utility and Heavy Contractors Association, Virginia Beach - 8 January 1986. (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Richard A. Gephardt Introduction, Richmond - 11 January 1986. (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Navy League, Richmond Council - 16 January 1986. (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Voter Registration Drive Committee Honoring Moses Riddick, Suffolk - 2 March 1986. (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - Virginia Association of Letter Carriers, Arlington - 10 March 1986. (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Child Safety Day, Petersburg - 22 March 1986. (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - St. Julien's Creek Citizens Meeting - 17 April 1986. (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - Subcontracting Opportunities Fair, Portsmouth - 18 April 1986. (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - Chesapeake Democratic Dinner - 26 April 1986. (Box 79, Folder 34)
  - Naval Civilian Administration Association, Silver Spring, Md. - 5 May 1986. (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - Virginia Beer Wholesalers Association - 6 May 1986. (Box 79, Folder 36)
  - Amelia Day Festival - 17 May 1986. (Box 79, Folder 37)
  - Sussex-Surry-Greensville County Improvement Association - 17 May 1986. (Box 79, Folder 38)
  - Friends of the Naval Museum - 19 May 1986. (Box 79, Folder 39)
  - Crater District Planning Commission - 22 May 1986. (Box 79, Folder 40)
  - Franklin/Southampton Chamber of Commerce - 23 May 1986. (Box 79, Folder 41)
  - Black Business Leaders of Portsmouth - 23 May 1986. (Box 79, Folder 42)
  - Memorial Day Parade, Portsmouth - 24 May 1986. (Box 79, Folder 43)
  - Southside Virginia Retired Officers Association, Ft. Lee - 29 May 1986. (Box 79, Folder 44)
  - St. Vincent/St. Paul High School Commencement, Petersburg - 1 June 1986. (Box 79, Folder 45)
  - Powhatan High School Commencement - 5 June 1986. (Box 79, Folder 46)
  - Arlington County Democratic Party - 7 June 1986. (Box 79, Folder 47)
  - Chesapeake General Hospital Obstetrics Wing Dedication - 22 June 1986. (Box 79, Folder 48)
  - Greater Hampton Roads Chamber of Commerce, Norfolk - 30 June 1986. (Box 79, Folder 49)
  - National Superintendents Association, Norfolk - 8 July 1986. (Box 79, Folder 50)
  - National Beer Wholesalers Association Executives, Alexandria - 10 July 1986. (Box 79, Folder 51)
  - AARP Chapter 1041, Colonial Heights - 12 September 1986. (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - National Beer Wholesalers Association Annual Convention, San Francisco - 16 September 1986. (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - "Richmond Day" Service, Spring Hill Baptist Church, Blackstone - 21 September 1986. (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - National Women's Political Caucus, Portsmouth - 27 September 1986. (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Greenbrier Elementary School Dedication - 28 September 1986. (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Anchor Industrial Park, Petersburg - 29 September 1986. (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Government Marketing Opportunties Fair, Petersburg - 6 October 1986. (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Iceland Summit (1986). (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - "Career Day" - Petersburg Rotary Club - 22 October 1986. (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Navy Day Luncheon, Portsmouth - 22 October 1986. (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Southside Area Democratic Women's Club, Petersburg - 25 October 1986. (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Petersburg Democratic Committee Annual Meeting - 25 October 1986. (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Loudoun County Democratic Dinner, Middleburg - 26 October 1986. (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Tri-Cities Senior Citizens Council, Petersburg - 30 October 1986. (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Health Insurance Fair - 1 November 1986. (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Mt. Herman Community League, Portsmouth - 6 November 1986. (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Churchland Kiwanis Club, Portsmouth - 7 November 1986. (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - AARP Crater Chapter 1399, Portsmouth - 10 November 1986. (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Fredericksburg/Spotsylvania County Democratic Dinner - 8 May 1986. (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Speech Index, 1987. (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Chesapeake Men for Progress Annual Banquet - 6 February 1987. (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, Virginia Beach - 4 March 1987. (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Metal Trades Council - 23 March 1987. (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, Williamsburg - 26 March 1987. (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Young Democrats Annual Convention, Williamsburg - 27 March 1987. (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Contact Old Dominion, Inc., Fort Lee - 3 April 1987. (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - United States Army Reserve Reunion, Petersburg - 4 April 1987. (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - Virginia Hospitality Association, Arlington - 9 April 1987. (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - Law Day Program, Petersburg - 1 May 1987. (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - Small Business Contracting Day Conference, Norfolk - 6 February 1987. (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - Chesapeake Jubilee Celebration - 16 May 1987. (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Annual Pilgrimage to St. Luke's Church - 17 May 1987. (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Crater District Planning Commission - 26 May 1987. (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - Southeastern Public Service Authority - 5 June 1987. (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - Western Branch High School Commencement, Chesapeake - 7 June 1987. (Box 80, Folder 35)
  - Harbor Tower Professional Tennis Tournament, Portsmouth - 13 June 1987. (Box 80, Folder 36)
  - Tidewater Community College Commencement, Norfolk - 14 June 1987. (Box 80, Folder 37)
  - Chorey Park Apartments Dedication, Suffolk - 27 June 1987. (Box 80, Folder 38)
  - Great Creek Watershed Project, Brunswick County - 27 June 1987. (Box 80, Folder 39)
  - Great Bridge Jaycees Banquet, Chesapeake - 2 July 1987. (Box 80, Folder 40)
  - Hodges Manor Civic League - 8 July 1987. (Box 80, Folder 41)
  - Virginia State Sheriffs' Association, Norfolk - 20 July 1987. (Box 80, Folder 42)
  - Hampton Roads Chamber of Commerce, Norfolk - 20 August 1987. (Box 80, Folder 43)
  - Suffolk Rotary Club - 20 August 1987. (Box 80, Folder 44)
  - AARP, Suffolk Chapter - 21 August 1987. (Box 80, Folder 45)
  - Retired Officers Association, Portsmouth Area Chapter - 21 August 1987. (Box 80, Folder 46)
  - Downtown Portsmouth Association, Inc. - 21 August 1987. (Box 80, Folder 47)
  - Suffolk Kiwanis Club - 24 August 1987. (Box 80, Folder 48)
  - Franklin/Southampton County Chamber of Commerce - 28 August 1987. (Box 80, Folder 49)
  - Tidewater Legal Aid Society, Norfolk - 12 September 1987. (Box 80, Folder 50)
  - Martha W. Davis Cancer Treatment Center Dedication, Portsmouth - 4 October 1987. (Box 80, Folder 51)
  - Southern Civic League - 9 October 1987. (Box 80, Folder 52)
  - Southside Electric Cooperative, Crewe - 16 October 1987. (Box 80, Folder 53)
  - Retired Personnel Seminar, Department of the Navy, Norfolk - 17 October 1987. (Box 80, Folder 54)
  - Senior Citizens' Health and Nutrition Workshops - 19 October 1987. (Box 80, Folder 55)
  - Union Camp Corporation Centennial, Franklin - 26 October 1987. (Box 80, Folder 56)
  - NAACP, Portsmouth Chapter - 7 November 1987. (Box 80, Folder 57)
  - Veteran's Day Ceremonies - 11 November 1987. (Box 80, Folder 58)
  - Southside Area Democratic Woman's Club, Petersburg - 21 November 1987. (Box 80, Folder 59)
  - Governor's Conference on Small Business, McLean - 17 September 1987. (Box 80, Folder 60)
  - Petersburg Annual Democratic Dinner - 24 October 1987. (Box 80, Folder 61)
  - Speech Index, 1988. (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Twentieth Annual Douglas MacArthur Memorial Dinner, Portsmouth - 23 January 1988. (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - American Federation of Government Employees - 5 February 1988. (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Air Force Association, Leigh Wade Chapter, Petersburg - 19 February 1988. (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - George Washington's 256th Birthday, Washington, D.C. - 22 February 1988. (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Quartermaster Corps Logistics Conference, Fort Lee - 26 February 1988. (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - C-17 Conference - 25 March 1988. (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Senior Management Development Conference, Anheuser-Busch, Chesterfield, MO - 12 April 1988. (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Seventh Annual Heritage Fair, Prince George - 16 April 1988. (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Association of General Contractors of Virginia - 20 April 1988. (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Navy Civilian Personnel Managers Association - 3 May 1988. (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Troop Support Agency Headquarters Dedication, Fort Lee - 6 May 1988. (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Memorial Breakfast for Police Officers, Colonial Heights - 13 May 1988. (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Small Business Contracting Day - 13 May 1988. (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Southside Emergency Crew Inc. Appreciation Dinner, Petersburg - 13 May 1988. (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - AIPAC Policy Conference Workshop, Washington, D.C. - 16 May 1988. (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Memorial Breakfast for Police Officers, Portsmouth - 20 May 1988. (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Democratic Convention - 4 June 1988. (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - "Day Care: Its Importance to Small Business" - 8 June 1988. (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Flag Day, Portsmouth - 1988. (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Navy Procurement Conference, Old Dominion University - 8 July 1988. (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Commission on Merchant Marine and Defense, Norfolk - 23 August 1988. (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - Central Civic Forum, Portsmouth - 24 August 1988. (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - Honoring the U.S. Constitution, Fort Lee - September 1988. (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - "Forgotten Widows" - 8 September 1988. (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Southside Democratic Women's Breakfast, Petersburg - 24 September 1988. (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - "The Hazard Communication Standard and its Impact on Small Business Non-Manufacturers - 28 September 1988. (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - Statement on Former Rep. David Satterfield III - 6 October 1988. (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - Hampton Roads Chamber of Commerce, Chesapeake - 18 October 1988. (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - Petersburg Chamber of Commerce - 26 October 1988. (Box 81, Folder 30)
  - Chesapeake Democratic Women's Club - 5 November 1988. (Box 81, Folder 31)
  - Speech Index, 1989. (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - Zuni Ruritan Club - 12 January 1989. (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - Hampton Roads Chamber of Commerce, Chesapeake Chapter - 14 January 1989. (Box 81, Folder 34)
  - Virginia Conference, United Methodist Women, Portsmouth - 21 January 1989. (Box 81, Folder 35)
  - MacArthur Memorial Dinner, Norfolk - 21 January 1989. (Box 81, Folder 37)
  - Norfolk Minority Business Development Center, Portsmouth - 17 February 1989. (Box 81, Folder 38)
  - Keneseth Beth Israel, Richmond - 26 February 1989. (Box 81, Folder 39)
  - Petersburg Clergy Association - 27 February 1989. (Box 81, Folder 40)
  - "Export Financing" - 1 March 1989. (Box 81, Folder 41)
  - Congregation Gomley Chesed, Portsmouth - 7 April 1989. (Box 81, Folder 42)
  - Virginia Federation of Democratic Women, Petersburg - 29 April 1989. (Box 81, Folder 43)
  - Nottoway County Bicentennial Celebration - 30 April 1989. (Box 81, Folder 44)
  - Congregation Brith Achim, Petersburg - 5 May 1989. (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Miles B. Carpenter Museum Opening, Waverly - 6 May 1989. (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Richard Bland College Commencement - 12 May 1989. (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Ninth Annual Small Business Contracting Day, Norfolk - 12 May 1989. (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Electronic Warfare Test and Development Center - 19 May 1989. (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - "New to Exporting" - 19 May 1989. (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Kenston Forest School Commencement, Blackstone - 2 June 1989. (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Benford Hunter Tribute, Suffolk - 4 June 1989. (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Association of Life Underwriters, Norfolk - 17 June 1989. (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Tidewater Child Care Association, Portsmouth - 17 June 1989. (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Navy Procurement Conference, Chesapeake - 23 June 1989. (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Petersburg Wagner Road Project Ceremony - 26 June 1989. (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Hopewell Moose Lodge - 4 July 1989. (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Landmark Apartments Opening, Chesapeake - 6 July 1989. (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Tracor Applied Sciences, Inc. Open House, Chesapeake - 7 August 1989. (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Allied-Signal Retirees, Hopewell - 18 August 1989. (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Retired Officers Association, Southside Virginia Chapter, Fort Lee - 18 August 1989. (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Commemorative Coin Presentation, Naval Shipyard Museum, Portsmouth - 24 August 1989. (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Speech Index, 1989-1990. (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - House Appropriations Committee, Subcommittee on Energy and Water Development - 5 April 1989. (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Senate Small Business Committee - 22 June 1989. (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Senate Small Business Subcommittee on Government Contracts and Paperwork Reduction - 7 September 1989. (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Subcontractors Association - 1 September 1989. (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Virginia State Council of Senior Citizens, Petersburg - 8 September 1989. (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - House Subcommittee on Exports, Tax Policy, and Special Problems - 12 September 1989. (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - House Subcommittee on Small Business - 13 September 1989. (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - D.A.R.E. Day Program, Portsmouth - 16 September 1989. (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - House Small Business Subcommittee on Exports, Tax Policy, and Special Problems, Richmond - 2 October 1989. (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - "Obstacles That Small Businesses Face in Obtaining Export Financing" - 11 October 1989. (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Shipyard Association, Portsmouth - 13 October 1989. (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Virginia Bankers Association, Emporia - 16 October 1989. (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Senate Small Business Committee - 17 October 1989. (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - "Portsmouth on the Move" Meeting - 23 October 1989. (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - Dr. Willa Bazemore Reception, Chesapeake - 28 October 1989. (Box 82, Folder 34)
  - Small Business Subcommittee on Antitrust, Impact of Deregulation and Privatization - 31 October 1989. (Box 82, Folder 35)
  - Health Insurance Fair for Federal Retirees, Chesapeake - 4 November 1989. (Box 82, Folder 36)
  - Doug Wilder Events - 4-5 November 1989. (Box 82, Folder 37)
  - U.S.S. Lincoln Commissioning - 11 November 1989. (Box 82, Folder 38)
  - Virginia Chamber of Commerce, Wakefield - 13 November 1989. (Box 82, Folder 39)
  - Hamilton West Ribbon Cutting, Petersburg 18 November 1989. (Box 82, Folder 40)
  - Petersburg Health and Human Services 50th Anniversary - 20 November 1989. (Box 82, Folder 41)
  - N. Duvall Flora Appreciation Dinner, Chesapeake - 30 November 1989. (Box 82, Folder 42)
  - Ruth Brown Celebration, Portsmouth - 12 January 1990. (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Douglas MacArthur Memorial Dinner - 27 January 1990. (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, Richmond - 10 February 1990. (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Coast Guard Exhibit, Portsmouth - 11 February 1990. (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Gerow Reserve Association, Fort Lee - 2 March 1990. (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Art Award Ceremony, Virginia Museum of Fine Arts - 4 March 1990. (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Small Business Subcommittee on Exports, Tax Policy, and Special Problems, Goldsboro, NC - 12 March 1990. (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Census Day, Southside District Census Office, Portsmouth - 1 April 1990. (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - "Alzheimer's: The Unmet Challenge for Research and Care" - 3 April 1990. (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Great Bridge Baseball Association, Chesapeake - 21 April 1990. (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Laboratory Testing and Certification - 30 April 1990. (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Small Business Contracting Day, Norfolk - 11 May 1990. (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Sportsman's Caucus, Washington, D.C. - 15 May 1990. (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - "Breast Cancer: Race for the Cure" - 16 May 1990. (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Consumer Protection and Infomercial Advertising - 18 May 1990. (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Living Memorial to U.S. Veterans Dedication - 19 May 1990. (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Portsmouth Naval Hospital Groundbreaking - 4 June 1990. (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - "Education for Tomorrow's Workforce" - 8 June 1990. (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Naval Submarine League - 14 June 1990. (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Suffolk Democratic Dinner - 14 June 1990. (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Chisolm House Benefit - 15 June 1990. (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Lynnhaven Borough Advisory Committee - 16 June 1990. (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - "Computer Technology: Impact on Productivity and Competitiveness" - 18 June 1990. (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Mt. Tabor Church of God in Christ, Smithfield - 16 June 1990. (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Speech Index, 1990-1991. (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - "Certification Problems Facing Small American Laboratories" - 26 June 1990. (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - "Hospital Charity Care and Tax Exempt Status" - 28 June 1990. (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - "Medicare and Medicaid's 25th Anniversary" - 30 June 1990. (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - General Electric New Engine Maintenance Center, Suffolk - 10 July 1990. (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - Navy Procurement Conference, Chesapeake - 20 July 1990. (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - Fourth District Housing Conference, Wakefield - 23 July 1990. (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - Fourth District Housing Conference-Introduction of Gov. Douglas Wilder, Wakefield - 23 July 1990. (Box 83, Folder 32)
  - Stone Container Corporation Dinner - August 1990. (Box 83, Folder 33)
  - Wal-Mart Groundbreaking, Dinwiddie County - 6 August 1990. (Box 83, Folder 34)
  - Army Corps of Engineers, Norfolk District, Change of Command - 14 August 1990. (Box 83, Folder 35)
  - Portsmouth Democratic Women's Council - 17 August 1990. (Box 83, Folder 36)
  - Chesapeake Democratic Committee - 21 September 1990. (Box 83, Folder 37)
  - Water Resources Development Act, Floor Statement - 25 September 1990. (Box 83, Folder 38)
  - Water Resources Development Act, Floor Statement - 25 September 1990. (Box 83, Folder 39)
  - "Banquet for the Homeless," (Jan Faircloth) - 6 October 1990. (Box 83, Folder 40)
  - National Infomercial Marketing Association - 23 October 1990. (Box 83, Folder 41)
  - Suffolk Agribusiness Appreciation Day - 29 October 1990. (Box 83, Folder 42)
  - Chesapeake Rotary Club - 31 October 1990. (Box 83, Folder 43)
  - Eagle Scout Court of Honor, Suffolk - 1 November 1990. (Box 83, Folder 44)
  - Simonsdale Civic Club - 5 November 1990. (Box 83, Folder 45)
  - "Operation Smile International" Luncheon, Chesapeake - 7 Deecember 1990. (Box 83, Folder 46)
  - Disabled American Veterans Home, Chesapeake - 8 December 1990. (Box 83, Folder 47)
  - Portsmouth Area Resources Coalition - 4 January 1991. (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Douglas MacArthur Chapter, Association of the U.S. Army, Portsmouth - 26 January 1991. (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - "Effects of Wetlands Protection Measures on Small Businesses" - 30 January 1991. (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - "Role of U.S. Small Business in Rebuilding Kuwait" - 11 March 1991. (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Rushmere Volunteer Fire Department - 23 March 1991. (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Five Points Battlefield Dedication - 23 March 1991. (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - "How to do Business in Kuwait," Portsmouth - 8 April 1991. (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Chesapeake Democratic Committee - 20 April 1991. (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - "Operation Homecoming," Norfolk - 5 May 1991. (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Appomattox Iron Works Ribbon Cutting - 31 May 1991. (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Petersburg Chamber of Commerce - 16 May 1991. (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Small Business Contracting Day, Norfolk - 17 May 1991. (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Emporia Armed Forces Day - 18 May 1991. (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Commission on Defense Base Closure and Realignment, Washington, D.C. - 4 June 1991. (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Contracting Day, Virginia Beach - 28 June 1991. (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Health Care Town Meeting, Chesapeake - 14 January 1991. (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Small Business Desert Storm Loan Relief Act - 27 February 1991. (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - James Madison Memorial Fellowship Program - 26 November 1991. (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - FY1992 Defense Authorization Bill, Floor Statement. (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Church Manor Apartments Opening, Smithfield (1991). (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Democratic Party Victory Dinner, Louisa (1990). (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Invasion of Kuwait (1990). (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Speech Index, 1991. (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - "Impact of Independent Contractor Reclassification on Small Business" - 30 July 1991. (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Congress Mid-Term Report Card - August 1991. (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - American-Israel Issues - 27 August 1991. (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Washington Ditch Trail Dedication, Great Dismal Swamp - 28 September 1991. (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - D.A.R.E. Family Day, Portsmouth - 28 September 1991. (Box 84, Folder 28)
  - Defense Commissary Agency, Fort Lee - 30 September 1991. (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - Petersburg Synagogue Homecoming - 11 October 1991. (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - Israel Bonds Award Presentation - 3 November 1991. (Box 84, Folder 31)
  - Tri-Cities Brunswick Stew Festival, Hopewell - 2 November 1991. (Box 84, Folder 32)
  - Great Bridge Intermediate School Dedication - 17 November 1991. (Box 84, Folder 33)
  - 43rd Virginia Conference on World Trade, Williamsburg - 4 October 1991. (Box 84, Folder 34)
  - Brasfield Dam Hydroelectric Power Facility Amendment - 23 October 1991. (Box 84, Folder 35)
  - Affordable Housing Conference, Suffolk - 18 November 1991. (Box 84, Folder 36)
  - Smithfield Chamber of Commerce - 6 December 1991. (Box 84, Folder 37)